(Sheldon:)...that, I maintain, in the right concentration
could be weaponized.
(Penny:)Leonard might come home.
Can we talk in my apartment?
(Sheldon:)We're not done?
(Howard:)- No.
- Eh, why not?
(Sheldon:)We're already through
the looking glass anyway.
(Penny:)Okay, so here's the thing.
(Penny:)I guess you're aware
that Leonard asked me out.
(Sheldon:)Well, he didn't actually say anything.
(Sheldon:)But when he came back to the apartment,
he was doing a dance...
(Sheldon:)...that brought to mind
the happy hippos in Fantasia.
(Penny:)Oh, that's nice.
(Penny:)Anyhow,
the thing I wanted to talk to about is...
(Penny:)...you know, since Leonard
and I have become friends, I was just...
Wanna sit down?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I wish it were that simple.
(Sheldon:)You see, I don't spend much time here,
and so I've never chosen a place to sit.
(Penny:)Well, choose.
(Sheldon:)There are a number of options and...
(Sheldon:)I'm really not familiar enough
with the cushion densities...